Contact

ramchandraawalekar@gmail.co m

919740331632

LinkedIn Profile

Top Skills · See all

Microsoft Office · Management · Microsoft Excel · Microsoft Word · Research · PowerPoint · Sales · Leadership · Training · Photoshop

Accomplishments · See all

4 Languages

Ram Awalekar

Sr. Manager-Research(Pheromones) at Pest Control India (Pvt) Ltd

Kolhapur, Maharashtra, India

Summary

Experienced Research Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the consumer services industry. Skilled in Pheromone Research and Development cum commercial production of Agricultural insects. Strong research professional with a Master's Degree focused in Agrochemicals and Pest management from Shivaji University.

Experience

Sr.Manager-Research (Pheromones) · Pest Control India (Pvt) Ltd May 1998 - Present · Bangalore, Karnataka (INDIA)

 $Sr.\ Manager-Research (Pheromones) \cdot {\tt Pest\ Control\ India\ (Pvt)\ Ltd}$

May 1998 - Present · Bangalore, India

Research and Development professional with Expert in Chemical synthesis of insect Pheromones(R & D cum commercial production) and Formulation of Bio-Pesticides.

Manager-Research(Pheromones) · Pest Control India (Pvt) Ltd

May 1998 - Present · Bengaluru Area, India

Research and Development professional with Expert in Chemical synthesis of insect Pheromones(R & D cum commercial production) and Formulation of Bio-Pesticides.

Ph.D.(Pursuing) · Shivaji University

July 2015 - May 2019 (3 years 11 months) · Kolhapur Area, India

Lab.Incharge · Sigma Galvanizing Private Ltd. Mumbai

December 1997 - April 1998 (5 months) · Mumbai Area, India

See all of Ram's experience

Education

Shivaji University

Master's Degree, Agrochemicals and Pest management (1995 - 1997)